<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="label_contact_us">Contact Us:</string>
    <string name="cta_chat_team_revibes">Chat Team Revibes</string>
    <string name="cta_your_point">Your Point</string>
    <string name="cta_help_center">HELP CENTER</string>
    <string name="cta_drop_off">Drop Off</string>
    <string name="cta_pick_up">Pick Up</string>
    <string name="cta_exchange_points">Exchange Points to Voucher</string>
    <string name="cta_shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="cta_transacion_history">My Transaction History</string>
    <string name="about_us">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="our_founder">OUR FOUNDER</string>
    <string name="our_founder_desc">Revibes was founded by Carissa Handrian, an aspiring sustainability activist, in 2023.\nThe name Revibes originates from 3 goals: Redefining what it means to raise awareness,\nRevolutionizing the methods of activity,\nand Reaching as far as possible.</string>
    <string name="our_goals">OUR GOALS</string>
    <string name="our_goals_desc">We aim to increase the levels of awareness of Societal and Environmental problems not just in Indonesia, but internationally as well.\nTo aid in this, we collaborate with other likeminded NGOs and communities.</string>
    <string name="our_brand">OUR BRAND</string>
    <string name="re_logo_content_desc">Globe inside R</string>
    <string name="re_logo_desc">Within the bold R, a globe icon is incorporated. This globe represents the global reach and impact of RevibeS, as well as our commitment to making sure that the problems that we are tackling go acknowledged on not just a local scale, but a global one. The Globe serves as a reminder that positive vibes can extend worldwide to promote a green and sustainable future.</string>
    <string name="vibe_logo_content_desc">vibe logo</string>
    <string name="vibe_logo_desc">The word “vibe” is written in a simple, lowercase, and basic font. This choice reflects the brand’s approachability and connection with individuals.</string>
    <string name="s_logo_content_desc">S icon</string>
    <string name="s_logo_desc">The final element, the letter “S,” is designed as a graphic arrowhead pointing upward. This graphic element, colored in a vibrant blue shade, represents progress, positivity, and the upward trajectory of sustainable development.</string>
</resources>